Finding Aid for the Buffalo Musicians' Association Records, 1889-2009
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Local 43 Records, 1889-1968, I.; 49 bound volumes, 23 boxes, 1 official stamp
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1889-1968, I.A; 9 bound volumes, 20 boxes
    - Board Meeting, January 16, 1959, 2 leaves (Box 16, Item 2097)
    - Special Board Meeting, January 20, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2098)
    - Board Meeting, January 22, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2099)
    - Board Meeting, January 30, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2100)
    - Board Meeting, February 6, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2101)
    - Board Meeting, February 13, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2102)
    - Board Meeting, February 20, 1959, 2 leaves (Box 16, Item 2103)
    - Board Meeting, February 27, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2104)
    - Board Meeting, March 6, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2105)
    - Board Meeting, March 13, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2106)
    - Special Board Meeting, March 18, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2107)
    - Board Meeting, March 20, 1959, 2 leaves (Box 16, Item 2108)
    - Special Section to Minutes of Special Board Meeting: Buffalo Symphony Orchestra Auditions, March 24, 1959, 2 leaves (Box 16, Item 2109)
    - Special Section: of Minutes of Special Meeting: on Matter of Re-engagement of Symphony Players, March 26, 1959, 2 leaves (Box 16, Item 2110)
    - Board Meeting, March 27, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2111)
    - Special Board Meeting, March 30, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2112)
    - Board Meeting, April 3, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2113)
    - Special Board Meeting, April 6, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2114)
    - Special Board Meeting, April 8, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2115)
    - Board Meeting, April 10, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2116)
    - Board Meeting, April 17, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2117)
    - Board Meeting, April 24, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2118)
    - Open Board Meeting, April 29, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2119)
    - Board Meeting, May 1, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2120)
    - Board Meeting, May 8, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2121)
    - Board Meeting, May 15, 1959, 2 leaves (Box 16, Item 2122)
    - Board Meeting, May 22, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2123)
    - Board Meeting, May 29, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2124)
    - Board Meeting, June 5, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2125)
    - Board Meeting, June 11, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2126)
    - Board Meeting, June 26, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2127)
    - Board Meeting, July 3, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2128)
    - Board Meeting, July 10, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2129)
    - Board Meeting, July 17, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2130)
    - Board Meeting, July 24, 1959, 1 leaves (Box 16, Item 2131)
    - Board Meeting, July 31, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2132)
    - Board Meeting, August 7, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2133)
    - Board Meeting, August 14, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2134)
    - Board Meeting, August 21, 1959, 2 leaves (Box 16, Item 2135)
    - Board Meeting, August 28, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2136)
    - Board Meeting, September 4, 1959, 2 leaves (Box 16, Item 2137)
    - Board Meeting, September 11, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2138)
    - Board Meeting, September 18, 1959, 2 leaves (Box 16, Item 2139)
    - Conference, September 19-20, 1959, 5 leaves (Box 16, Item 2140)
    - Board Meeting, September 25, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2141)
    - Board Meeting, October 2, 1959, 2 leaves (Box 16, Item 2142)
    - Board Meeting, October 9, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2143)
    - General Meeting, October 11, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2144)
    - Board Meeting, October 16, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2145)
    - Special Board Meeting, October 20, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2146)
    - Board Meeting, October 23, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2147)
    - Board Meeting, October 30, 1959, 2 leaves (Box 16, Item 2148)
    - Board Meeting, November 5, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2149)
    - Board Meeting, November 13, 1959, 2 leaves (Box 16, Item 2150)
    - Board Meeting, November 20, 1959, 2 leaves (Box 16, Item 2151)
    - Board Meeting, November 27, 1959, 2 leaves (Box 16, Item 2152)
    - Special Board Meeting, November 30, 1959, 3 leaves (Box 16, Item 2153)
    - Board Meeting, December 4, 1959, 2 leaves (Box 16, Item 2154)
    - Special Board Meeting, December 6, 1959, 3 leaves (Box 16, Item 2155)
    - Special Board Meeting, December 8, 1959, 2 leaves (Box 16, Item 2156)
    - Board Meeting, December 11, 1959, 2 leaves (Box 16, Item 2157)
    - Board Meeting, December 18, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2158)
    - Board Meeting, December 24, 1959, 1 leaf (Box 16, Item 2159)
    - Board Meeting, December 31, 1959, 4 leaves (Box 16, Item 2160)
    - Board Meeting, January 3, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2161)
    - Board Meeting, January 8, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2162)
    - General Meeting, January 10, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2163)
    - Board Meeting, January 15, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2164)
    - Board Meeting, January 22, 1960, 2 leaves (Box 17, Item 2165)
    - Board Meeting, January 29, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2166)
    - Special General Meeting, January 31, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2167)
    - Board Meeting, February 5, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2168)
    - Board Meeting, February 11, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2169)
    - Board Meeting, February 18, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2170)
    - Board Meeting, February 26, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2171)
    - Special Meeting, February 29, 1960, 2 leaves (Box 17, Item 2172)
    - Board Meeting, March 4, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2173)
    - Board Meeting, March 11, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2174)
    - Special Board Meeting, March 13, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2175)
    - Board Meeting, March 17, 1960, 2 leaves (Box 17, Item 2176)
    - Special Board Meeting with Buffalo Philharmonic Symphony, March 21, 1960, 2 leaves (Box 17, Item 2177)
    - Special Board Meeting, March 23, 1960, 4 leaves (Box 17, Item 2178)
    - Special Board Meeting, March 28, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2179)
    - Board Meeting, April 1, 1960, 2 leaves (Box 17, Item 2180)
    - Special General Meeting, April 4, 1960, 2 leaves (Box 17, Item 2181)
    - Special Board Meeting, April 5, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2182)
    - Board Meeting, April 8, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2183)
    - General Meeting, April 10, 1960, 3 leaves (Box 17, Item 2184)
    - Board Meeting, April 14, 1960, 3 leaves (Box 17, Item 2185)
    - Board Meeting, April 21, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2186)
    - Board Meeting, April 29, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2187)
    - Special Board Meeting, April 30, 1960, 2 leaves (Box 17, Item 2188)
    - Board Meeting, May 5, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2189)
    - Board Meeting, May 12, 1960, 2 leaves (Box 17, Item 2190)
    - Special General Meeting, May 15, 1960, 2 leaves (Box 17, Item 2191)
    - Board Meeting, May 19, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2192)
    - Special Board Meeting, May 21, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2193)
    - Board Meeting, May 26, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2194)
    - Board Meeting, June 2, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2195)
    - Board Meeting, June 16, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2196)
    - Board Meeting, June 23, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2197)
    - Board Meeting, June 30, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2198)
    - Board Meeting, July 7, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2199)
    - Board Meeting, July 14, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2200)
    - Board Meeting, July 21, 1960, 2 leaves (Box 17, Item 2201)
    - Board Meeting, July 28, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2202)
    - Board Meeting, August 4, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2203)
    - Board Meeting, August 11, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2204)
    - Board Meeting, August 18, 1960, 2 leaves (Box 17, Item 2205)
    - Board Meeting, August 25, 1960, 2 leaves (Box 17, Item 2206)
    - Board Meeting, September 2, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2207)
    - Board Meeting, September 9, 1960, 2 leaves (Box 17, Item 2208)
    - Board Meeting, September 15, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2209)
    - Board Meeting, September 22, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2210)
    - Special General Meeting, September 25, 1960, 2 leaves (Box 17, Item 2211)
    - Board Meeting, September 29, 1960, 2 leaves (Box 17, Item 2212)
    - Board Meeting, October 6, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2213)
    - Regular General Membership Meeting, October 9, 1960, 2 leaves (Box 17, Item 2214)
    - Special Board Meeting, October 12, 1960, 2 leaves (Box 17, Item 2215)
    - Board Meeting, October 13, 1960, 2 leaves (Box 17, Item 2216)
    - Special Board Meeting, October 17, 1960, 2 leaves (Box 17, Item 2217)
    - Board Meeting, October 20, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2218)
    - Special General Meeting, October 23, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2219)
    - Board Meeting, October 28, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2220)
    - Board Meeting, November 4, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2221)
    - Board Meeting, November 10, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2222)
    - Board Meeting, November 18, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2223)
    - Board Meeting, November 25, 1960, 3 leaves (Box 17, Item 2224)
    - Board Meeting, December 2, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2225)
    - Board Meeting, December 9, 1960, 3 leaves (Box 17, Item 2226)
    - Board Meeting, December 16, 1960, 4 leaves (Box 17, Item 2227)
    - Special Board Meeting, December 21, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2228)
    - Board Meeting, December 22, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2229)
    - Board Meeting, December 29, 1960, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2230)
    - Board Meeting, January 5, 1961, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2231)
    - Board Meeting, January 13, 1961, 2 leaves (Box 17, Item 2232)
    - Special Board Meeting, January 18, 1961, 2 leaves (Box 17, Item 2233)
    - Board Meeting, January 19, 1961, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2234)
    - Board Meeting, January 27, 1961, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2235)
    - Board Meeting, February 3, 1961, 2 leaves (Box 17, Item 2236)
    - Board Meeting, February 8, 1961, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2237)
    - Board Meeting, February 16, 1961, 3 leaves (Box 17, Item 2238)
    - Board Meeting, February 23, 1961, 3 leaves (Box 17, Item 2239)
    - Board Meeting, March 2, 1961, 2 leaves (Box 17, Item 2240)
    - Special Board Meeting, March 7, 1961, 2 leaves (Box 17, Item 2241)
    - Board Meeting, March 10, 1961, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2242)
    - Special Board Meeting, March 15, 1961, 3 leaves (Box 17, Item 2243)
    - Board Meeting, March 17, 1961, 3 leaves (Box 17, Item 2244)
    - Board Meeting, March 22, 1961, 2 leaves (Box 17, Item 2245)
    - Board Meeting, March 29, 1961, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2246)
    - Special Board Meeting, April 1, 1961, 2 leaves (Box 17, Item 2247)
    - Board Meeting, April 6, 1961, 2 leaves (Box 17, Item 2248)
    - Special Board Meeting, April 3, 1961, 3 leaves (Box 17, Item 2249)
    - Board Meeting, April 13, 1961, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2250)
    - Board Meeting, April 21, 1961, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2251)
    - Board Meeting, April 27, 1961, 2 leaves (Box 17, Item 2252)
    - Board Meeting, May 4, 1961, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2253)
    - Board Meeting, May 11, 1961, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2254)
    - Board Meeting, May 17, 1961, 2 leaves (Box 17, Item 2255)
    - Board Meeting, May 25, 1961, 2 leaves (Box 17, Item 2256)
    - Board Meeting, June 1, 1961, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2257)
    - Board Meeting, June 8, 1961, 2 leaves (Box 17, Item 2258)
    - Board Meeting, June 22, 1961, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2259)
    - Board Meeting, June 29, 1961, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2260)
    - Special Board Meeting, July 5, 1961, 2 leaves (Box 17, Item 2261)
    - Board Meeting, July 7, 1961, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2262)
    - Board Meeting, July 13, 1961, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2263)
    - Board Meeting, July 20, 1961, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2264)
    - Board Meeting, July 27, 1961, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2265)
    - Board Meeting, August 3, 1961, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2266)
    - Board Meeting, August 10, 1961, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2267)
    - Board Meeting, August 17, 1961, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2268)
    - Board Meeting, August 24, 1961, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2269)
    - Board Meeting, August 31, 1961, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2270)
    - Board Meeting, September 7, 1961, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2271)
    - Board Meeting, September 13, 1961, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2272)
    - Board Meeting, September 21, 1961, 5 leaves (Box 17, Item 2273)
    - Board Meeting, September 28, 1961, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2274)
    - Board Meeting, October 5, 1961, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2275)
    - General Meeting, October 8, 1961, 2 leaves (Box 17, Item 2276)
    - Board Meeting, October 12, 1961, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2277)
    - Board Meeting, October 19, 1961, 2 leaves (Box 17, Item 2278)
    - Board Meeting, October 26, 1961, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2279)
    - Board Meeting, November 2, 1961, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2280)
    - [Election of Officers], November 3, 1961, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2281)
    - Board Meeting, November 10, 1961, 2 leaves (Box 17, Item 2282)
    - Board Meeting, November 17, 1961, 2 leaves (Box 17, Item 2283)
    - Special Board Meeting, November 22, 1961, 2 leaves (Box 17, Item 2284)
    - Board Meeting, November 24, 1961, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2285)
    - Board Meeting, December 1, 1961, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2286)
    - Special Membership Meeting, December 4, 1961, 2 leaves (Box 17, Item 2287)
    - Board Meeting, December 7, 1961, 2 leaves (Box 17, Item 2288)
    - Special Board Meeting, December 11, 1961, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2289)
    - Board Meeting, December 14, 1961, 2 leaves (Box 17, Item 2290)
    - Board Meeting, December 21, 1961, 1 leaf (Box 17, Item 2291)
    - Board Meeting, December 27, 1961, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2292)
    - Special Board Meeting, January 2, 1962, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2293)
    - Installation and Regular Board Meeting, January 3, 1962, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2294)
    - Board Meeting, January 11, 1962, 3 leaves (Box 18, Item 2295)
    - Special Board Meeting, January 17, 1962, 1 leaf (Box 18, Item 2296)
    - Board Meeting, January 18, 1962, 1 leaf (Box 18, Item 2297)
    - Board Meeting, January 24, 1962, 1 leaf (Box 18, Item 2298)
    - Special Board Meeting, January 26, 1962, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2299)
    - Special Board Meeting, January 30, 1962, 3 leaves (Box 18, Item 2300)
    - Board Meeting, February 1, 1962, 1 leaf (Box 18, Item 2301)
    - Special Board Meeting, February 5, 1962, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2302)
    - Board Meeting, February 7, 1962, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2303)
    - Special Board Meeting, February 10, 1962, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2304)
    - Special Board Meeting, February 14, 1962, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2305)
    - Board Meeting, February 16, 1962, 1 leaf (Box 18, Item 2306)
    - Special Board Meeting, February 20, 1962, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2307)
    - Special Board Meeting, February 22, 1962, 3 leaves (Box 18, Item 2308)
    - Board Meeting, February 23, 1962, 1 leaf (Box 18, Item 2309)
    - Board Meeting, March 1, 1962, 1 leaf (Box 18, Item 2310)
    - Special Board Meeting, March 2, 1962, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2311)
    - Board Meeting, March 8, 1962, 1 leaf (Box 18, Item 2312)
    - Board Meeting, March 15, 1962, 1 leaf (Box 18, Item 2313)
    - Special Board Meeting, March 20, 1962, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2314)
    - Special Board Meeting, March 21, 1962, 1 leaf (Box 18, Item 2315)
    - Board Meeting, March 22, 1962, 3 leaves (Box 18, Item 2316)
    - Board Meeting, March 30, 1962, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2317)
    - Special Board Meeting, April 4, 1962, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2318)
    - Board Meeting, April 5, 1962, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2319)
    - General Meeting, April 8, 1962, 3 leaves (Box 18, Item 2320)
    - Special Board Meeting, April 9, 1962, 1 leaf (Box 18, Item 2321)
    - Special Board Meeting, April 10, 1962, 3 leaves (Box 18, Item 2322)
    - Special Board Meeting, April 12, 1962, 3 leaves (Box 18, Item 2323)
    - Board Meeting, April 13, 1962, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2324)
    - Special Membership Meeting, April 16, 1962, 4 leaves (Box 18, Item 2325)
    - Board Meeting, April 19, 1962, 1 leaf (Box 18, Item 2326)
    - Board Meeting, April 26, 1962, 1 leaf (Box 18, Item 2327)
    - Board Meeting, May 3, 1962, 1 leaf (Box 18, Item 2328)
    - Board Meeting, May 10, 1962, 1 leaf (Box 18, Item 2329)
    - Special Board Meeting, May 11, 1962, 4 leaves (Box 18, Item 2330)
    - Board Meeting, May 17, 1962, 3 leaves (Box 18, Item 2331)
    - Special Board Meeting, May 22, 1962, 4 leaves (Box 18, Item 2332)
    - Board Meeting, May 24, 1962, 1 leaf (Box 18, Item 2333)
    - Board Meeting, May 31, 1962, 4 leaves (Box 18, Item 2334)
    - Board Meeting, June 7, 1962, 3 leaves (Box 18, Item 2335)
    - Special Board Meeting, June 8, 1962, 4 leaves (Box 18, Item 2336)
    - Special Membership Meeting, June 18, 1962, 3 leaves (Box 18, Item 2337)
    - Board Meeting, June 21, 1962, 1 leaf (Box 18, Item 2338)
    - Special Membership Meeting, June 26, 1962, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2339)
    - Board Meeting, June 28, 1962, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2340)
    - Board Meeting, July 5, 1962, 1 leaf (Box 18, Item 2341)
    - Board Meeting, July 12, 1962, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2342)
    - [Telegram to House of Representatives], July 17, 1962, 1 leaf (Box 18, Item 2343)
    - Board Meeting, July 19, 1962, 1 leaf (Box 18, Item 2344)
    - Board Meeting, July 26, 1962, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2345)
    - Board Meeting, August 2, 1962, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2346)
    - Board Meeting, August 9, 1962, 1 leaf (Box 18, Item 2347)
    - Board Meeting, August 16, 1962, 3 leaves (Box 18, Item 2348)
    - Board Meeting, August 23, 1962, 1 leaf (Box 18, Item 2349)
    - Board Meeting, August 30, 1962, 3 leaves (Box 18, Item 2350)
    - Board Meeting, September 6, 1962, 4 leaves (Box 18, Item 2351)
    - Board Meeting, September 14, 1962, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2352)
    - Board Meeting and Special Board Meeting, September 20, 1962, 4 leaves (Box 18, Item 2353)
    - Board Meeting, September 27, 1962, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2354)
    - Board Meeting, October 4, 1962, 5 leaves (Box 18, Item 2355)
    - Board Meeting, October 11, 1962, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2356)
    - Board Meeting, October 18, 1962, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2357)
    - Board Meeting, October 26, 1962, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2358)
    - Board Meeting, November 2, 1962, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2359)
    - Board Meeting, November 9, 1962, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2360)
    - Board Meeting, November 16, 1962, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2361)
    - Board Meeting, November 23, 1962, 1 leaf (Box 18, Item 2362)
    - Board Meeting, November 29, 1962, 1 leaf (Box 18, Item 2363)
    - Board Meeting, December 7, 1962, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2364)
    - December 13, 1962, 1 leaf (Box 18, Item 2365)
    - Board Meeting, December 28, 1962, 5 leaves (Box 18, Item 2366)
    - Board Meeting, January 11, 1963, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2367)
    - Board Meeting, January 18, 1963, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2368)
    - Board Meeting, January 25, 1963, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2369)
    - Board Meeting, January 31, 1963, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2370)
    - Board Meeting, February 8, 1963, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2371)
    - Board Meeting, February 15, 1963, 1 leaf (Box 18, Item 2372)
    - Board Meeting, February 22, 1963, 1 leaf (Box 18, Item 2373)
    - Board Meeting, March 1, 1963, 1 leaf (Box 18, Item 2374)
    - Board Meeting, March 8, 1963, 1 leaf (Box 18, Item 2375)
    - Board Meeting, March 15, 1963, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2376)
    - Board Meeting, March 21, 1963, 1 leaf (Box 18, Item 2377)
    - Board Meeting, March 29, 1963, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2378)
    - Board Meeting, April 4, 1963, 1 leaf (Box 18, Item 2379)
    - Board Meeting, April 18, 1963, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2380)
    - Board Meeting, April 25, 1963, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2381)
    - Board Meeting, May 2, 1963, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2382)
    - Board Meeting, May 9, 1963, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2383)
    - Board Meeting, May 16, 1963, 1 leaf (Box 18, Item 2384)
    - Board Meeting, May 24, 1963, 1 leaf (Box 18, Item 2385)
    - Board Meeting, May 31, 1963, 1 leaf (Box 18, Item 2386)
    - Board Meeting, June 7, 1963, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2387)
    - Board Meeting, June 21, 1963, 3 leaves (Box 18, Item 2388)
    - Board Meeting, June 28, 1963, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2389)
    - Board Meeting, July 5, 1963, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2390)
    - Board Meeting, July 12, 1963, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2391)
    - Board Meeting, July 19, 1963, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2392)
    - Board Meeting, July 26, 1963, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2393)
    - Board Meeting, August 2, 1963, 1 leaf (Box 18, Item 2394)
    - Board Meeting, August 9, 1963, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2395)
    - Board Meeting, August 16, 1963, 3 leaves (Box 18, Item 2396)
    - Board Meeting, August 21, 1963, 3 leaves (Box 18, Item 2397)
    - Board Meeting, August 30, 1963, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2398)
    - Special Board Meeting, September 4, 1963, 1 leaf (Box 18, Item 2399)
    - Board Meeting, September 6, 1963, 4 leaves (Box 18, Item 2400)
    - Board Meeting, September 13, 1963, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2401)
    - Board Meeting, September 19, 1963, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2402)
    - Board Meeting, September 26, 1963, 3 leaves (Box 18, Item 2403)
    - Board Meeting, October 3, 1963, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2404)
    - Board Meeting, October 10, 1963, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2405)
    - Regular Membership Meeting, October 13, 1963, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2406)
    - Board Meeting, October 29, 1963, 1 leaf (Box 18, Item 2407)
    - Board Meeting, November 8, 1963, 4 leaves (Box 18, Item 2408)
    - Board Meeting, November 15, 1963, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2409)
    - Board Meeting, November 22, 1963, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2410)
    - Board Meeting, November 29, 1963, 1 leaf (Box 18, Item 2411)
    - Board Meeting, December 6, 1963, 3 leaves (Box 18, Item 2412)
    - Board Meeting, December 13, 1963, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2413)
    - Board Meeting, December 20, 1963, 1 leaf (Box 18, Item 2414)
    - Installation of Officer's and Executive Board and Regular Board Meeting, January 3, 1964, 3 leaves (Box 18, Item 2415)
    - Board Meeting, January 17, 1964, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2416)
    - Board Meeting, February 7, 1964, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2417)
    - Special Membership Meeting, February 16, 1964, 6 leaves (Box 18, Item 2418)
    - Board Meeting, March 6, 1964, 5 leaves (Box 18, Item 2419)
    - Board Meeting, March 13, 1964, 2 leaves (Box 18, Item 2420)
    - Special Membership Meeting, March 15, 1964, 1 leaf (Box 19, Item 2421)
    - Board Meeting, April 10, 1964, 2 leaves (Box 19, Item 2422)
    - Board Meeting, April 16, 1964, 2 leaves (Box 19, Item 2423)
    - Board Meeting, April 23, 1964, 2 leaves (Box 19, Item 2424)
    - Special Membership Meeting, May 10, 1964, 2 leaves (Box 19, Item 2425)
    - Board Meeting, May 21, 1964, 2 leaves (Box 19, Item 2426)
    - Board Meeting, May 28, 1964, 2 leaves (Box 19, Item 2427)
    - Board Meeting, June 4, 1964, 2 leaves (Box 19, Item 2428)
    - Board Meeting, June 11, 1964, 3 leaves (Box 19, Item 2429)
    - Board Meeting, June 25, 1964, 2 leaves (Box 19, Item 2430)
    - Board Meeting, July 2, 1964, 2 leaves (Box 19, Item 2431)
    - Board Meeting, July 9, 1964, 2 leaves (Box 19, Item 2432)
    - Board Meeting, July 16, 1964, 4 leaves (Box 19, Item 2433)
    - Special Membership Meeting, July 19, 1964, 2 leaves (Box 19, Item 2434)
    - Board Meeting, July 23, 1964, 3 leaves (Box 19, Item 2435)
    - Board Meeting, July 30, 1964, 5 leaves (Box 19, Item 2436)
    - Board Meeting, August 6, 1964, 2 leaves (Box 19, Item 2437)
    - Board Meeting, August 13, 1964, 2 leaves (Box 19, Item 2438)
    - Board Meeting, August 20, 1964, 1 leaf (Box 19, Item 2439)
    - Board Meeting, August 27, 1964, 6 leaves (Box 19, Item 2440)
    - Board Meeting, September 3, 1964, 2 leaves (Box 19, Item 2441)
    - Board Meeting, September 10, 1964, 1 leaf (Box 19, Item 2442)